flipbuilder.com 2019-05-29

# FlipBuilder Privacy Policy: we will not sell, share, or rent user information.[FlipBuilder.com]

Since our inception, FlipBuilder’s approach has been anchored with a strong commitment to privacy, security, compliance and transparency. This approach includes supporting our customers’ compliance with EU data protection requirements, including those set out in the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), which replaced the EU Data Protection Directive (also known as “Directive 95/46/EC“) and became enforceable on May 25, 2018.

FlipBuilder.com collects name, IP address and other information (such as e-mail address) on some parts of our website and registration service providers. This is done to help us provide you with the best customer service and with valuable information regarding relevant products and services from FlipBuilder.com.

FlipBuilder.com is dedicated to protecting personal information and will make every reasonable effort to handle collected information appropriately. All information collected, as well as related requests, will be handled as carefully and efficiently as possible in accordance with our standards for integrity and objectivity. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  

## Information We Collect & How we use 

No personal information is collected by FlipBuilder.com from visitors to our website, when viewing pages, or when downloading software from our website. We also do not collect or harvest the Email addresses of people who Email us directly. We only use them to respond to your queries, we collect information to provide better services to all of our users. We do use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. But IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

1\. Registration Information

All of our FlipBuilder.com programs can be used without registering, but if you want to register to create flip books without demo watermarks, you will be providing us with certain information, some of which identifies you personally, such as your name and email address, the product or service involved, the quantity or amount of the product. Personally identifiable information will never knowingly appear in public areas of our website. We will not share any of your information with any third parties. 

Credit Card information provided by you customer is used by MyCommerce, which handles all order issues of FlipBuilder.com products and services. We can't obtain your Credit Card information from MyCommerce. Credit Card numbers are confidential between you and MyCommerce. For more information about MyCommerce and their Privacy Policy please visit their website at <http://www.mycommerce.com/shopper-support>.

## 2\. Newsletter Information

If you subscribed our FlipBuilder Newsletter (it will be used to inform you of our products news and promotion only), your information will  **not**  be sold, rented or leased to a third-party, and you can remove your name and email from the list at any time.

3\. Contact Information

When you contact FlipBuilder.com, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our upgrade info about upcoming changes or improvements. 

**Sharing Information**

We do not sell Registration Information, nor any Newsletter or Contact Information with any third party for marketing purposes, unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific Flipbuilder product or service.

**Cookie and Remarketing**

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. FlipBuilder.com collects cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and we uses this information only internally - to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. 

FlipBuilder uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.  Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google advertising opt-out page") or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out page").

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Guidelines"), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465 "Google's Remarketing Policies"), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Restrictions").

## Links

FlipBuilder.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
